{
  "Python": [
    {
      "prompt": "Who developed the Python language?\n",
      "answer": ["Guido van Rossum"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What will be the output of the following code snippet? \nprint(2**3 + (5 + 6)**(1 + 1))\n",
      "answer": ["129"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "In which language is Python written?\n",
      "answer": ["C"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What is the method inside the class in python language?\n",
      "answer": ["function"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What is the correct extension of the Python file?\n",
      "answer": [".py"]
    }
  ],
  "General Knowledge": [
    {
      "prompt": "What is the largest country in the world?\n",
      "answer": ["Russia"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Which river is the longest in the world?\n",
      "answer": ["Nile"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Who was the first Prime Minister of India?\n",
      "answer": ["Jawaharlal Nehru", "Pandit Jawaharlal Nehru"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What is the chemical symbol for gold?\n",
      "answer": ["Au"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What currency is used in Japan?\n",
      "answer": ["Yen"]
    }
  ],
  "Sports": [
    {
      "prompt": "Who is the first and currently the only batsman to score double hundreds in four consecutive test series?\n",
      "answer": ["Virat Kohli"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "India has won the Hockey World Cup how many times?\n",
      "answer": ["1", "one"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Which country has won Football world Cup maximum times?\n",
      "answer": ["Brazil"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "How many team members are there on each side of a Kabaddi match?\n",
      "answer": ["7", "Seven"]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Which country has won the most Olympic Games gold medals?\n",
      "answer": ["United States", "The United States", "USA", "The United States of America"]
    }
  ]
}
